Bill 2 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 515 Addressing a motion to proceed under section 3101A of title 31, United States Code
Bill 3 - Vote On Approving the Journal
Bill 4 - Vote On Passage: H J RES 98 Relating to the disapproval of the President’s exercise of authority to increase the debt limit, as submitted under section 3101A of title 31, United States Code, on January 12, 2012
Bill 5 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 3117 Permanent Electronic Duck Stamp Act
Bill 6 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 1141 Rota Cultural and Natural Resources Study Act
Bill 7 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Agree: H RES 516 Expressing the sense of the House of Representatives that the passage of a fiscal year 2013 Federal budget is of national importance
Bill 8 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 2070 World War II Memorial Prayer Act of 2011
Bill 9 - Vote On Motion to Instruct Conferees: H R 3630 Temporary Payroll Tax Cut Continuation Act of 2011
Bill 10 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 1022 Buffalo Soldiers in the National Parks Study Act
Bill 11 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 3801 Ultralight Aircraft Smuggling Prevention Act
Bill 12 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 522 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 1173) to repeal the CLASS program
Bill 13 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 1 to H R 1173
Bill 14 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 2 to H R 1173
Bill 15 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 3 to H R 1173
Bill 16 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 4 to H R 1173
Bill 17 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 1173 Fiscal Responsibility and Retirement Security Act
Bill 18 - Vote On Passage: H R 1173 Fiscal Responsibility and Retirement Security Act
Bill 19 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 3835 To extend the pay limitation for Members of Congress and Federal employees
Bill 20 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 3567 Welfare Integrity Now for Children and Families Act of 2011
Bill 21 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 534 Providing for consideration of H.R. 3578, to amend the Balanced Budget and Emergency Deficit Control Act of 1985 to reform the budget baseline, and providing for consideration of H.R. 3582, to amend the Congressional Budget Act of 1974 to provide for macroeconomic analysis of the impact of legislation
Bill 22 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 534 Providing for consideration of H.R. 3578, to amend the Balanced Budget and Emergency Deficit Control Act of 1985 to reform the budget baseline, and providing for consideration of H.R. 3582, to amend the Congressional Budget Act of 1974 to provide for macroeconomic analysis of the impact of legislation
Bill 23 - Vote On Motion to Instruct Conferees: H R 3630 Temporary Payroll Tax Cut Continuation Act of 2011
Bill 24 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 1 to H R 3582
Bill 25 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 2 to H R 3582
Bill 26 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 4 to H R 3582
Bill 27 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 5 to H R 3582
Bill 28 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 8 to H R 3582
Bill 29 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 3582 To amend the Congressional Budget Act of 1974 to provide for macroeconomic analysis of the impact of legislation
Bill 30 - Vote On Passage: H R 3582 To amend the Congressional Budget Act of 1974 to provide for macroeconomic analysis of the impact of legislation
Bill 31 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 3578 To amend the Balanced Budget and Emergency Deficit Control Act of 1985 to reform the budget baseline
Bill 32 - Vote On Passage: H R 3578 To amend the Balanced Budget and Emergency Deficit Control Act of 1985 to reform the budget baseline
Bill 33 - Vote On Agreeing to the Conference Report: H R 658 FAA Modernization and Reform Act
Bill 34 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 537 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 1734) to decrease the deficit by realigning, consolidating, selling, disposing, and improving the efficiency of Federal buildings and other civilian real property, and for other purposes
Bill 35 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 1162 To provide the Quileute Indian Tribe Tsunami and Flood Protection, and for other purposes
Bill 36 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 2 to H R 1734
Bill 37 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 1734 Civilian Property Realignment Act
Bill 38 - Vote On Passage: H R 1734 Civilian Property Realignment Act
Bill 39 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 539 Providing for consideration of H.R. 3581, the Budget and Accounting Transparency Act of 2012
Bill 40 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 2 to H R 3581
Bill 41 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 3581 Budget and Accounting Transparency Act
Bill 42 - Vote On Passage: H R 3581 Budget and Accounting Transparency Act
Bill 43 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 540 Providing for the consideration of H.R. 3521, the Expedited Legislative Line-Item Veto and Rescissions Act
Bill 44 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 540 Providing for the consideration of H.R. 3521, the Expedited Legislative Line-Item Veto and Rescissions Act
Bill 45 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 2 to H R 3521
Bill 46 - Vote On Passage: H R 3521 To amend the Congressional Budget and Impoundment Control Act of 1974 to provide for a legislative line-item veto to expedite consideration of rescissions, and for other purposes
Bill 47 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: S 2038 To prohibit Members of Congress and employees of Congress from using nonpublic information derived from their official positions for personal benefit, and for other purposes
Bill 48 - Vote On Motion to Instruct Conferees: H R 3630 Temporary Payroll Tax Cut Continuation Act of 2011
Bill 49 - Vote On Approving the Journal
Bill 50 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 547 Providing for consideration of H.R. 3408, to set clear rules for the development of U.S. oil shale resources and promote shale technology research and development; consideration of H.R. 3813, to secure the annuities of Federal employees; and consideration of H.R. 7, to authorize funds for transportation safety programs
Bill 51 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 547 Providing for consideration of H.R. 3408, to set clear rules for the development of U.S. oil shale resources and promote shale technology research and development; consideration of H.R. 3813, to secure the annuities of Federal employees; and consideration of H.R. 7, to authorize funds for transportation safety programs
Bill 52 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 2079 To designate the facility of the United States Postal Service located at 10 Main Street in East Rockaway, New York, as the “John J. Cook Post Office”
Bill 53 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 3247 To designate the facility of the United States Postal Service located at 1100 Town and Country Commons in Chesterfield, Missouri, as the “Lance Corporal Matthew P. Pathenos Post Office Building”
Bill 54 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 3248 To designate the facility of the United States Postal Service located at 112 South 5th Street in Saint Charles, Missoui, as the “Lance Corporal Drew W. Weaver Post Office Building”
Bill 55 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 1 to H R 3408
Bill 56 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 2 to H R 3408
Bill 57 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 3 to H R 3408
Bill 58 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 4 to H R 3408
Bill 59 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 5 to H R 3408
Bill 60 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 7 to H R 3408
Bill 61 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 9 to H R 3408
Bill 62 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 11 to H R 3408
Bill 63 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 12 to H R 3408
Bill 64 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 13 to H R 3408
Bill 65 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 15 to H R 3408
Bill 66 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 16 to H R 3408
Bill 67 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 17 to H R 3408
Bill 68 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 18 to H R 3408
Bill 69 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 19 to H R 3408
Bill 70 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 3408 Protecting Investment in Oil Shale the Next Generation of Environmental, Energy, and Resource Security Act
Bill 71 - Vote On Passage: H R 3408 Protecting Investment in Oil Shale the Next Generation of Environmental, Energy, and Resource Security Act
Bill 72 - Vote On Agreeing to the Conference Report: H R 3630 To provide incentives for the creation of jobs, and for other purposes
Bill 73 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Concur in the Senate Amendment: H R 347 Federal Restricted Buildings and Grounds Improvement Act of 2011
Bill 74 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 563 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 2117) to prohibit the Department of Education from overreaching into academic affairs and program eligibility under title IV of the Higher Education Act of 1965
Bill 75 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 1 to H R 2117
Bill 76 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 4 to H R 2117
Bill 77 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 5 to H R 2117
Bill 78 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 2117 Protecting Academic Freedom in Higher Education Act
Bill 79 - Vote On Passage: H R 2117 Protecting Academic Freedom in Higher Education Act
Bill 80 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 566 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 1837) to address certain water-related concerns on the San Joaquin River, and for other purposes
Bill 81 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 566 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 1837) to address certain water-related concerns on the San Joaquin River, and for other purposes
Bill 82 - Vote On Approving the Journal
Bill 83 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 2 to H R 1837
Bill 84 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 3 to H R 1837
Bill 85 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 4 to H R 1837
Bill 86 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 5 to H R 1837
Bill 87 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 6 to H R 1837
Bill 88 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 7 to H R 1837
Bill 89 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 8 to H R 1837
Bill 90 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 1837 Sacramento-San Joaquin Valley Water Reliability Act
Bill 91 - Vote On Passage: H R 1837 Sacramento-San Joaquin Valley Water Reliability Act
Bill 92 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 562 Directing the Office of the Historian to compile oral histories from current and former Members of the House of Representatives involved in the historic and annual Selma to Montgomery, Alabama, marches, as well as the civil rights movement in general, for the purposes of expanding or augmenting the historic record
Bill 93 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: S 1134 St. Croix River Crossing Project Authorization Act
Bill 94 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Agree, as Amended: H RES 556 Condemning the Government of Iran for its continued persecution, imprisonment, and sentencing of Youcef Nadarkhani of the charge of apostasy
Bill 95 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 3637 Roy Schallern Rood Post Office Building
Bill 96 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 4105 To apply the countervailing duty provisions of the Tariff Act of 1930 to nonmarket economy countries, and for other purposes
Bill 97 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 570 Providing for consideration of H.R. 2842, the Bureau of Reclamation Small Conduit Hydropower Development and Rural Jobs Act
Bill 98 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 2 to H R 2842
Bill 99 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 2842 Bureau of Reclamation Small Conduit Hydropower Development and Rural Jobs Act
Bill 100 - Vote On Passage: H R 2842 Bureau of Reclamation Small Conduit Hydropower Development and Rural Jobs Act
Bill 101 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 572 Providing for consideration of H. R. 3606, to increase American job creation and economic growth by improving access to the public capital markets for emerging growth companies
Bill 102 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 572 Providing for consideration of H. R. 3606, to increase American job creation and economic growth by improving access to the public capital markets for emerging growth companies
Bill 103 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 3 to H R 3606
Bill 104 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 5 to H R 3606
Bill 105 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 6 to H R 3606
Bill 106 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 9 to H R 3606
Bill 107 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 15 to H R 3606
Bill 108 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 16 to H R 3606
Bill 109 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 3606 To increase American job creation and economic growth by improving access to the public capital markets for emerging growth companies
Bill 110 - Vote On Passage: H R 3606 To increase American job creation and economic growth by improving access to the public capital markets for emerging growth companies
Bill 111 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 3992 To allow otherwise eligible Israeli nationals to receive E-2 nonimmigrant visas if similarly situated United States nationals are eligible for similar nonimmigrant status in Israel
Bill 112 - Vote On Consideration of the Resolution: H RES 587 Providing for consideration of H. R. 2087, to remove restrictions from a parcel of land situated in the Atlantic District, Accomack County, Virginia
Bill 113 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 587 Providing for consideration of H. R. 2087, to remove restrictions from a parcel of land situated in the Atlantic District, Accomack County, Virginia
Bill 114 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 665 Excess Federal Building and Property Disposal Act
Bill 115 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 1 to H R 2087
Bill 116 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 2087 To remove restrictions from a parcel of land situated in the Atlantic District, Accomack County, Virginia
Bill 117 - Vote On Passage: H R 2087 To remove restrictions from a parcel of land situated in the Atlantic District, Accomack County, Virginia
Bill 118 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 591 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 5) to improve patient access to health care services and provide improved medical care by reducing the excessive burden the liability system places on the health care delivery system
Bill 119 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 591 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 5) to improve patient access to health care services and provide improved medical care by reducing the excessive burden the liability system places on the health care delivery system
Bill 120 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Concur in the Senate Amendment: H R 886 To require the Secretary of the Treasury to mint coins in commemoration of the 225th anniversary of the establishment of the Nation’s first Federal law enforcement agency, the United States Marshals Service
Bill 121 - Vote On Approving the Journal
Bill 122 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 1 to H R 5
Bill 123 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 2 to H R 5
Bill 124 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 5 to H R 5
Bill 125 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 5 To improve patient access to health care services and provide improved medical care by reducing the excessive burden the liability system places on the health care delivery system
Bill 126 - Vote On Passage: H R 5 To improve patient access to health care services and provide improved medical care by reducing the excessive burden the liability system places on the health care delivery system
Bill 127 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 2779 To exempt inter-affiliate swaps from certain regulatory requirements put in place by the Dodd-Frank Wall Street Reform and Consumer Protection Act
Bill 128 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 2682 Business Risk Mitigation and Price Stabilization Act
Bill 129 - Vote On Approving the Journal
Bill 130 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 595 Providing for consideration of H. R. 3309, Federal Communications Commission Process Reform Act of 2012
Bill 131 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 595 Providing for consideration of H. R. 3309, Federal Communications Commission Process Reform Act of 2012
Bill 132 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Concur in the Senate Amendment: H R 3606 To increase American job creation and economic growth by improving access to the public capital markets for emerging growth companies
Bill 133 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 3298 Homes for Heroes Act
Bill 134 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 1 to H R 3309
Bill 135 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 2 to H R 3309
Bill 136 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 4 to H R 3309
Bill 137 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 3309 To amend the Communications Act of 1934 to provide for greater transparency and efficiency in the procedures followed by the Federal Communications Commission
Bill 138 - Vote On Passage: H R 3309 To amend the Communications Act of 1934 to provide for greater transparency and efficiency in the procedures followed by the Federal Communications Commission
Bill 139 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 597 Providing for consideration of H. Con. Res. 112, establishing the budget for the United States Government for fiscal year 2013 and setting forth appropriate budgetary levels for fiscal years 2014 through 2022, and providing for consideration of motions to suspend the rules
Bill 140 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 597 Providing for consideration of H. Con. Res. 112, establishing the budget for the United States Government for fiscal year 2013 and setting forth appropriate budgetary levels for fiscal years 2014 through 2022, and providing for consideration of motions to suspend the rules
Bill 141 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 1339 To amend title 32, United States Code, the body of laws of the United States dealing with the National Guard, to recognize the City of Salem, Massachusetts, as the Birthplace of the National Guard of the United States
Bill 142 - Vote On Approving the Journal
Bill 143 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 1 to H CON RES 112
Bill 144 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 2 to H CON RES 112
Bill 145 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 3 to H CON RES 112
Bill 146 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 600 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 4281) to provide an extension of Federal-aid highway, highway safety, motor carrier safety, transit, and other programs funded out of the Highway Trust Fund pending enactment of a multiyear law reauthorizing such programs, and for other purposes
Bill 147 - Vote On Passage: H R 4281 To provide an extension of Federal-aid highway, highway safety, motor carrier safety, transit, and other programs funded out of the Highway Trust Fund pending enactment of a multiyear law reauthorizing such programs
Bill 148 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 4 to H CON RES 112
Bill 149 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 5 to H CON RES 112
Bill 150 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 6 to H CON RES 112
Bill 151 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H CON RES 112 Establishing the budget for the United States Government for fiscal year 2013 and setting forth appropriate budgetary levels for fiscal years 2014 through 2022
Bill 152 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 3001 Raoul Wallenberg Centennial Celebration Act
Bill 153 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 4040 To provide for the award of a gold medal on behalf of Congress to Jack Nicklaus in recognition of his service to the Nation in promoting excellence and good sportsmanship in golf
Bill 154 - Vote On Question of Consideration of the Resolution: H RES 614 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 4089) to protect and enhance opportunities for recreational hunting, fishing and shooting, and for other purposes
Bill 155 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 614 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 4089) to protect and enhance opportunities for recreational hunting, fishing and shooting, and for other purposes
Bill 156 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 614 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 4089) to protect and enhance opportunities for recreational hunting, fishing and shooting, and for other purposes
Bill 157 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 1815 Lena Horne Recognition Act
Bill 158 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 2 to H R 4089
Bill 159 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 3 to H R 4089
Bill 160 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 4 to H R 4089
Bill 161 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 7 to H R 4089
Bill 162 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 8 to H R 4089
Bill 163 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 4089 Sportsmen’s Heritage Act of 2012
Bill 164 - Vote On Passage: H R 4089 Sportsmen’s Heritage Act of 2012
Bill 165 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 619 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 4348) to provide an extension of Federal-aid highway, highway safety, motor carrier safety, transit, and other programs funded out of the Highway Trust Fund pending enactment of multiyear law reauthorizing such programs, and for other purposes
Bill 166 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 619 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 4348) to provide an extension of Federal-aid highway, highway safety, motor carrier safety, transit, and other programs funded out of the Highway Trust Fund pending enactment of multiyear law reauthorizing such programs, and for other purposes
Bill 167 - Vote On Approving the Journal
Bill 168 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 2 to H R 4348
Bill 169 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 4348 To provide an extension of Federal-aid highway, highway safety, motor carrier safety, transit, and other programs funded out of the Highway Trust Fund pending enactment of a multiyear law reauthorizing such programs, and for other purposes
Bill 170 - Vote On Passage: H R 4348 To provide an extension of Federal-aid highway, highway safety, motor carrier safety, transit, and other programs funded out of the Highway Trust Fund pending enactment of a multiyear law reauthorizing such programs, and for other purposes
Bill 171 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 2453 Mark Twain Commemorative Coin Act
Bill 172 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 620 Providing for consideration of H.R. 9, Small Business Tax Cut Act
Bill 173 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution, as Amended: H RES 620 Providing for consideration of H.R. 9, Small Business Tax Cut Act
Bill 174 - Vote On Approving the Journal
Bill 175 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 1 to H R 9
Bill 176 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 9 Small Business Tax Cut Act
Bill 177 - Vote On Passage: H R 9 Small Business Tax Cut Act
Bill 178 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 2157 To facilitate a land exchange involoving certain National Forest System lands in the Inyo National Forest, and for other purposes
Bill 179 - Vote On Motion to Instruct Conferees: H R 4348 To provide an extension of Federal-aid highway, highway safety, motor carrier safety, transit, and other programs funded out of the Highway Trust Fund pending enactment of a multiyear law reauthorizing such programs, and for other purposes
Bill 180 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 3336 Small Business Credit Availability Act
Bill 181 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 1038 To authorize the conveyance of two small parcels of land within the boundaries of the Coconino National Forest containing private improvements that were developed based upon the reliance of the landowners in an erroneous survey conducted in May 1960
Bill 182 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 631 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 3523) Cyber Intelligence Sharing and Protection Act; providing for consideration of motions to suspend the rules; providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 4628) to extend student loan interest rates for undergraduate Federal Direct Stafford Loans
Bill 183 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 631 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 3523) Cyber Intelligence Sharing and Protection Act; providing for consideration of motions to suspend the rules; providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 4628) to extend student loan interest rates for undergraduate Federal Direct Stafford Loans
Bill 184 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 1 to H R 3523
Bill 185 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 3 to H R 3523
Bill 186 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 4 to H R 3523
Bill 187 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 5 to H R 3523
Bill 188 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 6 to H R 3523
Bill 189 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 10 to H R 3523
Bill 190 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 12 to H R 3523
Bill 191 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 3523 To provide for the sharing of certain cyber threat intelligence and cyber threat information between the intelligence community and cybersecurity entities, and for other purposes
Bill 192 - Vote On Passage: H R 3523 To provide for the sharing of certain cyber threat intelligence and cyber threat information between the intelligence community and cybersecurity entities, and for other purposes
Bill 193 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 2096 To advance cybersecurity research, development, and technical standards, and for other purposes
Bill 194 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 4628 To extend student loan interest rates for undergraduate Federal Direct Stafford Loans
Bill 195 - Vote On Passage: H R 4628 To extend student loan interest rates for undergraduate Federal Direct Stafford Loans
Bill 196 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Agree: H CON RES 105 Authorizing the use of Emancipation Hall in the Capitol Visitor Center for an event to celebrate the birthday of King Kamehameha
Bill 197 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Agree: H CON RES 117 Authorizing the use of the Capitol Grounds for the National Peace Officers’ Memorial Service
Bill 198 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Agree: H CON RES 118 Authorizing the use of the Capitol Grounds for the District of Columbia Special Olympics Law Enforcement Torch Run
Bill 199 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 643 Providing for consideration of H.R. 5326, making appropriations for the Departments of Commerce and Justice, Science, and Related Agencies for the fiscal year ending September 30, 2013, and for other purposes
Bill 200 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 643 Providing for consideration of H.R. 5326, making appropriations for the Departments of Commerce and Justice, Science, and Related Agencies for the fiscal year ending September 30, 2013, and for other purposes
Bill 201 - Vote On Approving the Journal
Bill 202 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 1 to H R 5326
Bill 203 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 2 to H R 5326
Bill 204 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 3 to H R 5326
Bill 205 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 5 to H R 5326
Bill 206 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 8 to H R 5326
Bill 207 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 6 to H R 5326
Bill 208 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 11 to H R 5326
Bill 209 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 12 to H R 5326
Bill 210 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 14 to H R 5326
Bill 211 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 15 to H R 5326
Bill 212 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 17 to H R 5326
Bill 213 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 20 to H R 5326
Bill 214 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 22 to H R 5326
Bill 215 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 23 to H R 5326
Bill 216 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 24 to H R 5326
Bill 217 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 25 to H R 5326
Bill 218 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 26 to H R 5326
Bill 219 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 27 to H R 5326
Bill 220 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 30 to H R 5326
Bill 221 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 32 to H R 5326
Bill 222 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 33 to H R 5326
Bill 223 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 34 to H R 5326
Bill 224 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 2072 To reauthorize the Export-Import Bank of the United States, and for other purposes
Bill 225 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 4133 To express the sense of Congress regarding the United States-Israel strategic relationship, to direct the President to submit to Congress reports on United States actions to enhance this relationship and to assist in the defense of Israel, and for other purposes
Bill 226 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 35 to H R 5326
Bill 227 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 36 to H R 5326
Bill 228 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 37 to H R 5326
Bill 229 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 39 to H R 5326
Bill 230 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 41 to H R 5326
Bill 231 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 42 to H R 5326
Bill 232 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 44 to H R 5326
Bill 233 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 45 to H R 5326
Bill 234 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 46 to H R 5326
Bill 235 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 63 to H R 5326
Bill 236 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 47 to H R 5326
Bill 237 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 48 to H R 5326
Bill 238 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 51 to H R 5326
Bill 239 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 52 to H R 5326
Bill 240 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 54 to H R 5326
Bill 241 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 55 to H R 5326
Bill 242 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 60 to H R 5326
Bill 243 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 61 to H R 5326
Bill 244 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 648 Providing for consideration of H.R. 5652 to provide for reconciliation pursuant to section 201 of the concurrent resolution on the budget for fiscal year 2013
Bill 245 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 648 Providing for consideration of H.R. 5652 to provide for reconciliation pursuant to section 201 of the concurrent resolution on the budget for fiscal year 2013
Bill 246 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 5652 To provide for reconciliation pursuant to section 201 of the concurrent resolution on the budget for fiscal year 2013
Bill 247 - Vote On Passage: H R 5652 To provide for reconciliation pursuant to section 201 of the concurrent resolution on the budget for fiscal year 2013
Bill 248 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 5326 Making appropriations for the Departments of Commerce and Justice, Science, and Related Agencies for the fiscal year ending September 30, 2013, and for other purposes
Bill 249 - Vote On Passage: H R 5326 Making appropriations for the Departments of Commerce and Justice, Science, and Related Agencies for the fiscal year ending September 30, 2013, and for other purposes
Bill 250 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 365 To encourage, enhance, and integrate Blue Alert plans throughout the United States in order to disseminate information when a law enforcement officer is seriously injured or killed in the line of duty
Bill 251 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 3874 To provide for the conveyance of eight cemeteries that are located on National Forest System land in Black Hills National Forest, South Dakota
Bill 252 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 205 To amend the Act titled “An Act to authorize the leasing of restricted Indian lands for public, religious, educational, recreational, residential, business, and other purposes requiring the grant of long-term leases”, to provide for Indian tribes to enter into leases without approval from the Secretary of the Interior
Bill 253 - Vote On Question of Consideration of the Resolution: H RES 656 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 4970) to reauthorize the Violence Against Women Act of 1994, and providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 4310) National Defense Authorization Act for Fiscal Year 2013
Bill 254 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 656 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 4970) to reauthorize the Violence Against Women Act of 1994, and providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 4310) National Defense Authorization Act for Fiscal Year 2013
Bill 255 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 656 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 4970) to reauthorize the Violence Against Women Act of 1994, and providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 4310) National Defense Authorization Act for Fiscal Year 2013
Bill 256 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 4119 Border Tunnel Prevention Act of 2012
Bill 257 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 4970 To reauthorize the Violence Against Women Act of 1994
Bill 258 - Vote On Passage: H R 4970 To reauthorize the Violence Against Women Act of 1994
Bill 259 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 661 Providing for further consideration of H.R. 4310, National Defense Authorization Act for Fiscal Year 2013
Bill 260 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 661 Providing for further consideration of H.R. 4310, National Defense Authorization Act for Fiscal Year 2013
Bill 261 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Agree, as Amended: H RES 568 Expressing the sense of the House of Representatives regarding the importance of preventing the Government of Iran from acquiring a nuclear weapons capability
Bill 262 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 5740 To extend the National Flood Insurance Program, and for other purposes
Bill 263 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 4 to H R 4310
Bill 264 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 5 to H R 4310
Bill 265 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 6 to H R 4310
Bill 266 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 7 to H R 4310
Bill 267 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 8 to H R 4310
Bill 268 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 11 to H R 4310
Bill 269 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 12 to H R 4310
Bill 270 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 29 to H R 4310
Bill 271 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 28 to H R 4310
Bill 272 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 14 to H R 4310
Bill 273 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 15 to H R 4310
Bill 274 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 16 to H R 4310
Bill 275 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 17 to H R 4310
Bill 276 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 19 to H R 4310
Bill 277 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 20 to H R 4310
Bill 278 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 22 to H R 4310
Bill 279 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 23 to H R 4310
Bill 280 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 24 to H R 4310
Bill 281 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 25 to H R 4310
Bill 282 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 27 to H R 4310
Bill 283 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 30 to H R 4310
Bill 284 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 31 to H R 4310
Bill 285 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 32 to H R 4310
Bill 286 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 37 to H R 4310
Bill 287 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 38 to H R 4310
Bill 288 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 42 to H R 4310
Bill 289 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 44 to H R 4310
Bill 290 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 4310 National Defense Authorization Act for Fiscal Year 2013
Bill 291 - Vote On Passage: H R 4310 National Defense Authorization Act for Fiscal Year 2013
Bill 292 - Vote On Barrow Motion to Instruct Conferees: H R 4348 To provide an extension of Federal-aid highway, highway safety, motor carrier safety, transit, and other programs funded out of the Highway Trust Fund pending enactment of a multiyear law reauthorizing such programs, and for other purposes
Bill 293 - Vote On Rahall Motion to Instruct Conferees: H R 4348 To provide an extension of Federal-aid highway, highway safety, motor carrier safety, transit, and other programs funded out of the Highway Trust Fund pending enactment of a multiyear law reauthorizing such programs, and for other purposes
Bill 294 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 5651 Prescription Drug User Fee Amendments of 2012
Bill 295 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 4201 Servicemember Family Protection Act
Bill 296 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 915 Jamie Zapata Border Enforcement Security Task Force Act
Bill 297 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 667 Providing for consideration of the bills (H.R. 5743) Intelligence Authorization Act for FY 2013; (H.R. 5854) Military construction, the Department of Veterans Affairs Appropriation; (H.R. 5855) Department of Homeland Security Appropriation; and (H.R. 5325) Energy and Water Development Appropriation
Bill 298 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 667 Providing for consideration of the bills (H.R. 5743) Intelligence Authorization Act for FY 2013; (H.R. 5854) Military construction, the Department of Veterans Affairs Appropriation; (H.R. 5855) Department of Homeland Security Appropriation; and (H.R. 5325) Energy and Water Development Appropriation
Bill 299 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 3541 Prenatal Non-discrimination Act (PRENDA) of 2012
Bill 300 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 5743 Intelligence Authorization Act for Fiscal Year 2013
Bill 301 - Vote On Passage: H R 5743 Intelligence Authorization Act for Fiscal Year 2013
Bill 302 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 7 to H R 5854
Bill 303 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 15 to H R 5854
Bill 304 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 5854 Making appropriations for military construction, the Department of Veterans Affairs, and related agencies for the fiscal year ending September 30, 2013, and for other purposes
Bill 305 - Vote On Passage: H R 5854 Making appropriations for military construction, the Department of Veterans Affairs, and related agencies for the fiscal year ending September 30, 2013, and for other purposes
Bill 306 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 1 to H R 5325
Bill 307 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 3 to H R 5325
Bill 308 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 6 to H R 5325
Bill 309 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 8 to H R 5325
Bill 310 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 11 to H R 5325
Bill 311 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 9 to H R 5325
Bill 312 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 7 to H R 5325
Bill 313 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 10 to H R 5325
Bill 314 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 12 to H R 5325
Bill 315 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 14 to H R 5325
Bill 316 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 15 to H R 5325
Bill 317 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 16 to H R 5325
Bill 318 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 18 to H R 5325
Bill 319 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 44 to H R 5325
Bill 320 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 46 to H R 5325
Bill 321 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 19 to H R 5325
Bill 322 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 42 to H R 5325
Bill 323 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 37 to H R 5325
Bill 324 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 47 to H R 5325
Bill 325 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 24 to H R 5325
Bill 326 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 36 to H R 5325
Bill 328 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 31 to H R 5325
Bill 329 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 23 to H R 5325
Bill 330 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 28 to H R 5325
Bill 331 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 20 to H R 5325
Bill 332 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 22 to H R 5325
Bill 333 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 26 to H R 5325
Bill 334 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 27 to H R 5325
Bill 335 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 33 to H R 5325
Bill 336 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 48 to H R 5325
Bill 337 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 59 to H R 5325
Bill 338 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 49 to H R 5325
Bill 339 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 56 to H R 5325
Bill 340 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 17 to H R 5325
Bill 341 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 5325 Making appropriations for energy and water development and related agencies for the fiscal year ending September 30, 2013, and for other purposes
Bill 342 - Vote On Passage: H R 5325 Making appropriations for energy and water development and related agencies for the fiscal year ending September 30, 2013, and for other purposes
Bill 343 - Vote On Flake Motion to Instruct Conferees: H R 4348 To provide an extension of Federal-aid highway, highway safety, motor carrier safety, transit, and other programs funded out of the Highway Trust Fund pending enactment of a multiyear law reauthorizing such programs, and for other purposes
Bill 344 - Vote On Doggett Motion to Instruct Conferees: H R 4348 To provide an extension of Federal-aid highway, highway safety, motor carrier safety, transit, and other programs funded out of the Highway Trust Fund pending enactment of a multiyear law reauthorizing such programs, and for other purposes
Bill 345 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 2 to H R 5855
Bill 346 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 3 to H R 5855
Bill 347 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 4 to H R 5855
Bill 348 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 6 to H R 5855
Bill 349 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 14 to H R 5855
Bill 350 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 10 to H R 5855
Bill 351 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 22 to H R 5855
Bill 352 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 7 to H R 5855
Bill 353 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 11 to H R 5855
Bill 354 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 12 to H R 5855
Bill 355 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 18 to H R 5855
Bill 356 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 23 to H R 5855
Bill 357 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 24 to H R 5855
Bill 358 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 679 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 436) to amend the Internal Revenue Code of 1986 to repeal the excise tax on medical devices, and providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 5882) making appropriations for the Legislative Branch for fiscal year ending September 30, 2013, and for other purposes
Bill 359 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 679 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 436) to amend the Internal Revenue Code of 1986 to repeal the excise tax on medical devices, and providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 5882) making appropriations for the Legislative Branch for fiscal year ending September 30, 2013, and for other purposes
Bill 360 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 436 Protect Medical Innovation Act of 2012
Bill 361 - Vote On Passage: H R 436 Protect Medical Innovation Act of 2012
Bill 362 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 32 to H R 5855
Bill 363 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 33 to H R 5855
Bill 364 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 34 to H R 5855
Bill 365 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 35 to H R 5855
Bill 366 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 37 to H R 5855
Bill 367 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 40 to H R 5855
Bill 368 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 41 to H R 5855
Bill 369 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 5855 Making appropriations for the Department of Homeland Security for the fiscal year ending September 30, 2013, and for other purposes
Bill 370 - Vote On Passage: H R 5855 Making appropriations for the Department of Homeland Security for the fiscal year ending September 30, 2013, and for other purposes
Bill 371 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 1 to H R 5882
Bill 372 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 2 to H R 5882
Bill 373 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 4 to H R 5882
Bill 374 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 5 to H R 5882
Bill 375 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 7 to H R 5882
Bill 376 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 5882 Making appropriations for the Legislative Branch for the fiscal year ending September 30, 2013, and for other purposes
Bill 377 - Vote On Passage: H R 5882 Making appropriations for the Legislative Branch for the fiscal year ending September 30, 2013, and for other purposes
Bill 378 - Vote On Broun of Georgia Motion to Instruct Conferees: H R 4348 To provide an extension of Federal-aid highway, highway safety, motor carrier safety, transit, and other programs funded out of the Highway Trust Fund pending enactment of a multiyear law reauthorizing such programs, and for other purposes
Bill 379 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: S 684 To provide for the conveyance of certain parcels of land to the town of Alta, Utah
Bill 380 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: S 404 To modify a land grant patent issued by the Secretary of the Interior
Bill 381 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 688 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 2578) to amend the Wild and Scenic Rivers Act related to a segment of the Lower Merced River in California, and for other purposes
Bill 382 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 688 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 2578) to amend the Wild and Scenic Rivers Act related to a segment of the Lower Merced River in California, and for other purposes
Bill 383 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 2 to H R 2578
Bill 384 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 3 to H R 2578
Bill 385 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 5 to H R 2578
Bill 386 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 2578 To amend the Wild and Scenic Rivers Act related to a segment of the Lower Merced River in California, and for other purposes
Bill 387 - Vote On Passage: H R 2578 To amend the Wild and Scenic Rivers Act related to a segment of the Lower Merced River in California, and for other purposes
Bill 388 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 2938 Gila Bend Indian Reservation Lands Replacement Clarification Act
Bill 389 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 691 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 4480), the Strategic Energy Production Act
Bill 390 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 691 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 4480), the Strategic Energy Production Act
Bill 391 - Vote On Walz of Minnesota Motion to Instruct Conferees: H R 4348 To provide an extension of Federal-aid highway, highway safety, motor carrier safety, transit, and other programs funded out of the Highway Trust Fund pending enactment of a multiyear law reauthorizing such programs, and for other purposes
Bill 392 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 1 to H R 4480
Bill 393 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 6 to H R 4480
Bill 394 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 7 to H R 4480
Bill 395 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 8 to H R 4480
Bill 396 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 10 to H R 4480
Bill 397 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 11 to H R 4480
Bill 398 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 12 to H R 4480
Bill 399 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 13 to H R 4480
Bill 400 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 14 to H R 4480
Bill 401 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 15 to H R 4480
Bill 402 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 16 to H R 4480
Bill 403 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 17 to H R 4480
Bill 404 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 18 to H R 4480
Bill 405 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 20 to H R 4480
Bill 406 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 21 to H R 4480
Bill 407 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 23 to H R 4480
Bill 408 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 24 to H R 4480
Bill 409 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 4480 Strategic Energy Production Act of 2012
Bill 410 - Vote On Passage: H R 4480 Strategic Energy Production Act of 2012
Bill 411 - Vote On McKinley of West Virginia Motion to Instruct Conferees: H R 4348 To provide an extension of Federal-aid highway, highway safety, motor carrier safety, transit, and other programs funded out of the Highway Trust Fund pending enactment of a multiyear law reauthorizing such programs, and for other purposes
Bill 412 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 697 Providing for consideration of H.R. 5973, Agriculture Appropriations 2013, and providing for consideration of H.R. 5972, Transportation, and Housing and Urban Development Appropriations 2013
Bill 413 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 697 Providing for consideration of H.R. 5973, Agriculture Appropriations 2013, and providing for consideration of H.R. 5972, Transportation, and Housing and Urban Development Appropriations 2013
Bill 414 - Vote On Hoyer of Maryland Motion to Instruct Conferees: H R 4348 To provide an extension of Federal-aid highway, highway safety, motor carrier safety, transit, and other programs funded out of the Highway Trust Fund pending enactment of a multiyear law reauthorizing such programs, and for other purposes
Bill 415 - Vote On Black of Tennessee Motion to Instruct Conferees: H R 4348 To provide an extension of Federal-aid highway, highway safety, motor carrier safety, transit, and other programs funded out of the Highway Trust Fund pending enactment of a multiyear law reauthorizing such programs, and for other purposes
Bill 416 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 2 to H R 5972
Bill 417 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 5 to H R 5972
Bill 418 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 10 to H R 5972
Bill 419 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 14 to H R 5972
Bill 420 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 15 to H R 5972
Bill 421 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 8 to H R 5972
Bill 422 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 9 to H R 5972
Bill 423 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 12 to H R 5972
Bill 424 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 17 to H R 5972
Bill 425 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 18 to H R 5972
Bill 426 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 19 to H R 5972
Bill 427 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 20 to H R 5972
Bill 428 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 21 to H R 5972
Bill 429 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 23 to H R 5972
Bill 430 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 24 to H R 5972
Bill 431 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 35 to H R 5972
Bill 432 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 36 to H R 5972
Bill 433 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 26 to H R 5972
Bill 434 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 27 to H R 5972
Bill 435 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 29 to H R 5972
Bill 436 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 30 to H R 5972
Bill 437 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 708 Relating to the consideration of House Report 112-546 and an accompanying resolution, and providing for consideration of the resolution (H. Res. 706) authorizing the Committee on Oversight and Government Reform to initiate or intervene in judicial proceedings to enforce certain subpoenas.
Bill 438 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 4251 Securing Maritime Activites through Risk-based Targeting (SMART) for Port Security Act
Bill 439 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 4005 Gauging American Port Security (GAPS) Act
Bill 440 - Vote On Motion to Refer the Resolution to Oversight and Government Reform: H RES 711 Recommending that the House of Representatives find Eric H. Holder Jr., Attorney General, U.S. Department of Justice, in contempt of Congress for refusal to comply with a subpoena duly issued by the Committee on Oversight and Government Reform
Bill 441 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 711 Recommending that the House of Representatives find Eric H. Holder Jr., Attorney General, U.S. Department of Justice, in contempt of Congress for refusal to comply with a subpoena duly issued by the Committee on Oversight and Government Reform
Bill 442 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 706 Authorizing the Committee on Oversight and Government Reform to initiate or intervene in judicial proceedings to enforce certain subpoenas
Bill 443 - Vote On Motion to Table: H RES 718 Raising a question of the privileges of the House
Bill 444 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 717 Providing for consideration of H.R. 5856, Defense Appropriations for FY 2013; consideration of H.R. 6020, Financial Services and General Government Appropriations for FY 2013; consideration of the conference report to accompany H.R. 4348, the Surface Transportation Extension Act of 2012, Part II
Bill 445 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 38 to H R 5972
Bill 446 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 39 to H R 5972
Bill 447 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 51 to H R 5972
Bill 448 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 52 to H R 5972
Bill 449 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 5972 Making appropriations for the Departments of Transportation, and Housing and Urban Development, and related agencies for the fiscal year ending September 30, 2013, and for other purposes
Bill 450 - Vote On Passage: H R 5972 Making appropriations for the Departments of Transportation, and Housing and Urban Development, and related agencies for the fiscal year ending September 30, 2013, and for other purposes
Bill 451 - Vote On Agreeing to the Conference Report: H R 4348 To provide an extension of Federal-aid highway, highway safety, motor carrier safety, transit, and other programs funded out of the Highway Trust Fund pending enactment of a multiyear law reauthorizing such programs, and for other purposes
Bill 452 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 4155 To direct the head of each Federal department and agency to treat relevant military training as sufficient to satisfy training or certification requirements for Federal licenses
Bill 453 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 4367 To amend the Electronic Fund Transfer Act to limit the fee disclosure requirement for an automatic teller machine to the screen of that machine
Bill 454 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 5892 Hydropower Regulatory Efficiency Act of 2012
Bill 455 - Vote On Motion to Adjourn
Bill 456 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 724 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 6079) to repeal the Patient Protection and Affordable Care Act and health care-related provisions in the Health Care and Education Reconciliation Act of 2010
Bill 457 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 724 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 6079) to repeal the Patient Protection and Affordable Care Act and health care-related provisions in the Health Care and Education Reconciliation Act of 2010
Bill 458 - Vote On Approving the Journal
Bill 459 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 6079 To repeal the Patient Protection and Affordable Care Act and health care-related provisions in the Health Care and Education Reconciliation Act 2010
Bill 460 - Vote On Passage: H R 6079 To repeal the Patient Protection and Affordable Care Act and health care-related provisions in the Health Care and Education Reconciliation Act 2010
Bill 461 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 726 Providing for consideration of H.R. 4402, to require the Secretary of the Interior and the Secretary of Agriculture to more efficiently develop domestic sources of the minerals and mineral materials of strategic and critical importance to United States economic and national security and manufacturing competitiveness
Bill 462 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 1 to H R 4402
Bill 463 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 2 to H R 4402
Bill 464 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 3 to H R 4402
Bill 465 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 4 to H R 4402
Bill 466 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 7 to H R 4402
Bill 467 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 4402 National Strategic and Critical Minerals Production Act
Bill 468 - Vote On Passage: H R 4402 National Strategic and Critical Minerals Production Act
Bill 469 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 6018 Foreign Relations Authorization Act, Fiscal Year 2013
Bill 470 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: S 2009 Insular Areas Act of 2011
Bill 471 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 5872 Sequestration Transparency Act of 2012
Bill 472 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 1 to H R 5856
Bill 473 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 3 to H R 5856
Bill 474 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 14 to H R 5856
Bill 475 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 15 to H R 5856
Bill 476 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 16 to H R 5856
Bill 477 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 17 to H R 5856
Bill 478 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 18 to H R 5856
Bill 479 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 24 to H R 5856
Bill 480 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 23 to H R 5856
Bill 481 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 27 to H R 5856
Bill 482 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 28 to H R 5856
Bill 483 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 29 to H R 5856
Bill 484 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 34 to H R 5856
Bill 485 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 37 to H R 5856
Bill 486 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 38 to H R 5856
Bill 487 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 39 to H R 5856
Bill 488 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 42 to H R 5856
Bill 489 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 44 to H R 5856
Bill 490 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 46 to H R 5856
Bill 491 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 47 to H R 5856
Bill 492 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 49 to H R 5856
Bill 493 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 50 to H R 5856
Bill 494 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 53 to H R 5856
Bill 495 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 54 to H R 5856
Bill 496 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 56 to H R 5856
Bill 497 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 58 to H R 5856
Bill 498 - Vote On Passage: H R 5856 Making appropriations for the Department of Defense for the fiscal year ending September 30, 2013, and for other purposes
Bill 499 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 2362 Indian Tribal Trade and Investment Demonstration Project Act of 2011
Bill 500 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: S 2039 To allow a State or local government to construct levees on certain properties otherwise designated as open space lands
Bill 501 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 3477 To designate the facility of the United States Postal Service located at 133 Hare Road in Crosby, Texas, as the Army First Sergeant David McNerney Post Office Building
Bill 502 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 738 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 4078), Regulatory Freeze for Jobs Act of 2012, and providing for the bill (H.R. 6082), Congressional Replacement of President Obama’s Energy-Restricting and Job-Limiting Offshore Drilling Plan, and for other purposes
Bill 503 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 738 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 4078), Regulatory Freeze for Jobs Act of 2012, and providing for the bill (H.R. 6082), Congressional Replacement of President Obama’s Energy-Restricting and Job-Limiting Offshore Drilling Plan, and for other purposes
Bill 504 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 2 to H R 6082
Bill 505 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 4 to H R 6082
Bill 506 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 5 to H R 6082
Bill 507 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 6 to H R 6082
Bill 508 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 7 to H R 6082
Bill 509 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 8 to H R 6082
Bill 510 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 6082 Congressional Replacement of President Obama’s Energy-Restricting and Job-Limiting Offshore Drilling Plan
Bill 511 - Vote On Passage: H R 6082 Congressional Replacement of President Obama’s Energy-Restricting and Job-Limiting Offshore Drilling Plan
Bill 512 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 6168 President Obama’s Proposed 2010-2017 Offshore Drilling Lease Sale Plan Act
Bill 513 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 459 To require a full audit of the Board of Governors of the Federal Reserve System and the Federal reserve banks by the Comptroller General of the United States before the end of 2012, and for other purposes
Bill 514 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 1 to H R 4078
Bill 515 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 2 to H R 4078
Bill 516 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 3 to H R 4078
Bill 517 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 4 to H R 4078
Bill 518 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 5 to H R 4078
Bill 519 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 741 Providing for further consideration of the bill (H.R. 4078) to provide that no agency may take any significant regulatory action until the unemployment rate is equal to or less than 6.0 percent
Bill 520 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 6 to H R 4078
Bill 521 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 7 to H R 4078
Bill 522 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 8 to H R 4078
Bill 523 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 9 to H R 4078
Bill 524 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 10 to H R 4078
Bill 525 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 11 to H R 4078
Bill 526 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 12 to H R 4078
Bill 527 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 13 to H R 4078
Bill 528 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 15 to H R 4078
Bill 529 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 16 to H R 4078
Bill 530 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 17 to H R 4078
Bill 531 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 18 to H R 4078
Bill 532 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 19 to H R 4078
Bill 533 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 20 to H R 4078
Bill 534 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 23 to H R 4078
Bill 535 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 4078 To provide that no agency may take any significant regulatory action until the unemployment rate is equal to or less than 6.0 percent
Bill 536 - Vote On Passage: H R 4078 To provide that no agency may take any significant regulatory action until the unemployment rate is equal to or less than 6.0 percent
Bill 537 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: S 679 To reduce the number of executive positions subject to Senate confirmation
Bill 538 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 828 Federal Employee Tax Accountability Act of 2012
Bill 539 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 3803 District of Columbia Pain-Capable Unborn Child Protection Act
Bill 540 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 747 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 6169) Pathway to Job Creation through a Simpler, Fairer Tax Code Act of 2012; providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 8) Job Protection and Recession Prevention Act and providing for consideration of motions to suspend the rules
Bill 541 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 1 to H RES 747
Bill 542 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution, as Amended: H RES 747 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 6169) Pathway to Job Creation through a Simpler, Fairer Tax Code Act of 2012; providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 8) Job Protection and Recession Prevention Act and providing for consideration of motions to suspend the rules
Bill 543 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 1 to H R 8
Bill 544 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 8 To extend certain tax relief provisions enacted in 2001 and 2003, and for other purposes
Bill 545 - Vote On Passage: H R 8 To extend certain tax relief provisions enacted in 2001 and 2003, and for other purposes
Bill 546 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Agree: H RES 750 Providing for the concurrence by the House in the Senate amendment to H.R. 1905, with an amendment
Bill 547 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 4365 To amend title 5, United States Code, to make clear that accounts in the Thrift Savings Fund are subject to certain Federal tax levies
Bill 548 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 752 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 6233) to make supplemental agricultural disaster assistance available for fiscal year 2012 with the costs of such assistance offset by changes to certain conservation programs, and for other purposes
Bill 549 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 752 Providing for consideration of the bill (H.R. 6233) to make supplemental agricultural disaster assistance available for fiscal year 2012 with the costs of such assistance offset by changes to certain conservation programs, and for other purposes
Bill 550 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 1 to H R 6169
Bill 551 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 6169 To provide for expedited consideration of a bill providing for comprehensive tax reform
Bill 552 - Vote On Passage: H R 6169 To provide for expedited consideration of a bill providing for comprehensive tax reform
Bill 553 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 6233 Agricultural Disaster Assistance Act of 2012
Bill 554 - Vote On Passage: H R 6233 Agricultural Disaster Assistance Act of 2012
Bill 555 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Agree: H CON RES 127 Expressing the sense of Congress regarding actions to preserve and advance the multistakeholder governance model under which the Internet has thrived
Bill 556 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: S CON RES 56 Providing for a conditional adjournment or recess of the Senate and an adjournment of the House of Representatives
Bill 557 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 6122 To revise the authority of the Librarian of Congress to accept gifts and bequests on behalf of the Library, and for other purposes
Bill 558 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 2139 Lions Clubs International Century of Service Commemorative Coin Act
Bill 559 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 6186 To require a study of voluntary community-based flood insurance options and how such options could be incorporated into the national flood insurance program
Bill 560 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 773 Providing for consideration of H.R. 5544, to authorize and expedite a land exchange involving National Forest System land in the State of Minnesota for the public school system, and for consideration of H.R. 5949, to extend the FISA Amendments Act of 2008 for 5 years
Bill 561 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 773 Providing for consideration of H.R. 5544, to authorize and expedite a land exchange involving National Forest System land in the State of Minnesota for the public school system, and for consideration of H.R. 5949, to extend the FISA Amendments Act of 2008 for 5 years
Bill 562 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 4264 FHA Emergency Fiscal Solvency Act
Bill 563 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 1 to H R 5544
Bill 564 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 2 to H R 5544
Bill 565 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 3 to H R 5544
Bill 566 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 4 to H R 5544
Bill 567 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 5544 Minnesota Education Investment and Employment Act
Bill 568 - Vote On Passage: H R 5544 Minnesota Education Investment and Employment Act
Bill 569 - Vote On Passage: H R 5949 To extend the FISA Amendments Act of 2008 for five years
Bill 570 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 3857 Public Transit Security and Local Law Enforcement Support Act
Bill 571 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 5865 American Manufacturing Competitiveness Act of 2012
Bill 572 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 778 Providing for consideration of H.J. Res. 117, making continuing appropriations for fiscal year 2013, and for other purposes; H.R. 6365, the National Security and Job Protection Act
Bill 573 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 778 Providing for consideration of H.J. Res. 117, making continuing appropriations for fiscal year 2013, and for other purposes; H.R. 6365, the National Security and Job Protection Act
Bill 574 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 779 Providing for consideration of H.R. 6213, the No More Solyndras Act
Bill 575 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 1775 Stolen Valor Act
Bill 576 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 6365 National Security and Job Protection Act
Bill 577 - Vote On Passage: H R 6365 National Security and Job Protection Act
Bill 578 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H J RES 117 Making continuing appropriations for fiscal year 2013, and for other purposes
Bill 579 - Vote On Passage: H J RES 117 Making continuing appropriations for fiscal year 2013, and for other purposes
Bill 580 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: S 3245 To extend by 3 years the authorization of the EB-5 Regional Center Program, the E-Verify Program, the Special Immigrant Nonminister Religious Worker Program, and the Conrad State 30 J-1 Visa Waiver Program
Bill 581 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 1 to H R 6213
Bill 582 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 2 to H R 6213
Bill 583 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 6213 No More Solyndras Act
Bill 584 - Vote On Passage: H R 6213 No More Solyndras Act
Bill 585 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 5044 To amend the Internal Revenue Code of 1986 to exclude from gross income any discharge of indebtedness income on education loans of deceased veterans
Bill 586 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 5912 To amend the Internal Revenue Code of 1986 to prohibit the use of public funds for political party conventions, and to provide for the return of previously distributed funds for deficit reduction
Bill 587 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 788 Providing for consideration of (H.J.Res. 118) and (H.R. 3409)
Bill 588 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 788 Providing for consideration of (H.J.Res. 118) and (H.R. 3409)
Bill 589 - Vote On Passage: H J RES 118 Providing for congressional disapproval of the rule submitted by the Office of Family Assistance of the Administration for Children and Families of the Department of HHS relating to waiver and expenditure authority under the Social Security Act with respect to the Temporary Assistance for Needy Families program
Bill 590 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 6429 To amend the Immigration and Nationality Act to promote innovation, investment, and research in the United States, to eliminate the diversity immigrant program, and for other purposes
Bill 591 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 5987 To establish the Manhattan Project National Historical Park in Oak Ridge, Tennessee, Los Alamos, New Mexico, and Hanford, Washington, and for other purposes
Bill 592 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 1 to H R 3409
Bill 593 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 3 to H R 3409
Bill 594 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 4 to H R 3409
Bill 595 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 5 to H R 3409
Bill 596 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 8 to H R 3409
Bill 597 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 9 to H R 3409
Bill 598 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 10 to H R 3409
Bill 599 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 11 to H R 3409
Bill 600 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 12 to H R 3409
Bill 601 - Vote On Agreeing to the Amendment: Amendment 13 to H R 3409
Bill 602 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 3409 To limit the authority of the Secretary of the Interior to issue regulations before December 31, 2013, under the Surface Mining Control and Reclamation Act of 1977
Bill 603 - Vote On Passage: H R 3409 To limit the authority of the Secretary of the Interior to issue regulations before December 31, 2013, under the Surface Mining Control and Reclamation Act of 1977
Bill 604 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 6371 Streamlining Claims Processing for Federal Contractor Employees Act
Bill 605 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 808 Providing for consideration of H.R. 6156, to authorize the extension of nondiscriminatory treatment (normal trade relations treatment) to products of the Russian Federation and Moldova and to require reports on the compliance of the Russian Federation with its obligations as a member of the World Trade Organization
Bill 606 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 808 Providing for consideration of H.R. 6156, to authorize the extension of nondiscriminatory treatment (normal trade relations treatment) to products of the Russian Federation and Moldova and to require reports on the compliance of the Russian Federation with its obligations as a member of the World Trade Organization
Bill 607 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Concur in the Senate Amendments: H R 2453 Mark Twain Commemorative Coin Act
Bill 608 - Vote On Passage: H R 6156 Russia and Moldova Jackson-Vanik Repeal Act of 2012
Bill 609 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 5997 Medical Preparedness Allowable Use Act
Bill 610 - Vote On motion to Suspend the Rules and Concur in the Senate Amendment: H R 915 Jamie Zapata Border Enforcement Security Task Force Act
Bill 611 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 821 Providing for consideration of H.R. 6429, STEM Jobs Act of 2012
Bill 612 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 6429 To amend the Immigration and Nationality Act to promote innovation, investment, and research in the United States, to eliminate the diversity immigrant program, and for other purposes
Bill 613 - Vote On Passage: H R 6429 To amend the Immigration and Nationality Act to promote innovation, investment, and research in the United States, to eliminate the diversity immigrant program, and for other purposes
Bill 614 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 6582 American Energy Manufacturing Technical Corrections Act
Bill 615 - Vote On Approving the Journal
Bill 616 - Vote On Motion to Adjourn
Bill 617 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Agree: S CON RES 50 Expressing the sense of Congress regarding actions to preserve and advance the multistakeholder governance model under which the Internet has thrived
Bill 618 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 6602 To make revisions in title 36, United States Code, as necessary to keep the title current and make technical corrections and improvements
Bill 619 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: S 2367 To strike the word “lunatic” from Federal law, and for other purposes
Bill 620 - Vote On Approving the Journal
Bill 621 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 827 Providing for consideration of motions to suspend the rules
Bill 622 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 827 Providing for consideration of motions to suspend the rules
Bill 623 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 6190 Asthma Inhalers Relief Act
Bill 624 - Vote On Motion to Instruct Conferees: H R 4310 National Defense Authorization Act for Fiscal Year 2013
Bill 625 - Vote On Motion to Permit Closed Conference Meetings: H R 4310 National Defense Authorization Act for Fiscal Year 2013
Bill 626 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 4053 To intensify efforts to identify, prevent, and recover payment error, waste, fraud, and abuse within Federal spending
Bill 627 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 4606 To authorize the issuance of right-of-way permits for natural gas pipelines in Glacier National Park, and for other purposes
Bill 628 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: S 3193 To make technical corrections to the legal description of certain land to be held in trust for the Barona Band of Mission Indians, and for other purposes
Bill 629 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 6504 Small Business Investment Company Modernization Act
Bill 630 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Agree to the Senate Amendment: H R 3783 An act to provide for a comprehensive strategy to counter Iran’s growing hostile presence and activity in the Western Hemisphere, and for other purposes
Bill 631 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 6621 To correct and improve certain provisions of the Leahy-Smith America Invents Act and title 35, United States Code
Bill 632 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: S 3642 Theft of Trade Secrets Clarification Act
Bill 633 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 6672 To reauthorize certain programs under the Public Health Service Act and the Federal Food, Drug, and Cosmetic Act with respect to public health security and all-hazards preparedness and response, and for other purposes
Bill 634 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 1845 To provide for a study on issues relating to access to intravenous immune globulin (IVIG) for Medicare beneficiaries in all care settings and a demonstration project to examine the benefits of providing coverage and payment for items and services necessary to administer IVIG in the home
Bill 635 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Agree, as Amended: H RES 668 To refer H.R. 5862, a bill making congressional reference to the United States Court of Federal Claims pursuant to sections 1492 and 2509 of title 28, United States Code, the Indian trust-related claims of the Quapaw Tribe of Oklahoma (O-Gah-Pah) as well as its individual members
Bill 636 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 6655 Protect our Kids Act
Bill 637 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: S 3564 Public Interest Declassification Board Reauthorization Act
Bill 638 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 6016 Government Employee Accountability Act
Bill 639 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 841 Providing for consideration of the Senate amendment to H.J. Res. 66, approving the renewal of impact restrictions contained in the Burmese Freedom and Democracy Act of 2003; and providing for consideration of H.R. 6684, Spending Reduction Act of 2012
Bill 640 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 841 Providing for consideration of the Senate amendment to H.J. Res. 66, approving the renewal of impact restrictions contained in the Burmese Freedom and Democracy Act of 2003; and providing for consideration of H.R. 6684, Spending Reduction Act of 2012
Bill 641 - Vote On Ordering the Previous Question: H RES 840 Providing for consideration of the conference report to accompany H.R. 4310, National Defense Authorization Act for Fiscal Year 2013
Bill 642 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 840 Providing for consideration of the conference report to accompany H.R. 4310, National Defense Authorization Act for Fiscal Year 2013
Bill 643 - Vote On Motion to Recommit with Instructions: H R 6684 Spending Reduction Act of 2012
Bill 644 - Vote On Passage: H R 6684 Spending Reduction Act of 2012
Bill 645 - Vote On Agreeing to the Conference Report: H R 4310 National Defense Authorization Act for Fiscal Year 2013
Bill 646 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 3197 To name the Department of Veterans Affairs medical center in Spokane, Washington as the “Mann-Grandstaff Department of Veteran’s Affairs Medical Center”
Bill 647 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 6443 To designate the facility of the Department of Veterans Affairs located at 9800 West Commercial Boulevard in Sunrise, Florida as the “William ’Bill’ Kling VA Clinic”
Bill 648 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: S 925 Mt. Andrea Lawrence Designation Act
Bill 649 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass, as Amended: H R 3159 Foreign Aid Transparency and Accountability Act
Bill 650 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Concur in the Senate Amendment: H R 4057 To amend title 38, United States Code, to direct the Secretary of Veterans Affairs to develop a comprehensive policy to improve outreach and transparency to veterans and members of the Armed Forces through the provision of information on institutions of higher learning
Bill 651 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: S 3202 Dignified Burial and Other Veterans’ Benefits Improvement Act
Bill 652 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: S 3454 Intelligence Authorization Act for Fiscal Year 2013
Bill 653 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 6612 To redesignate the Dryden Flight Research Center as the Neil A. Armstrong Flight Research Center and the Western Aeronautical Test Range as the Hugh L. Dryden Aeronautical Test Range
Bill 654 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Concur in the Senate Amendment: H R 6364 World War I Centennial Commission Act
Bill 655 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Pass: H R 6726 To prevent the 2013 pay adjustment for Members of Congress and persons holding other offices or positions in the Federal Government from being made
Bill 656 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Concur in the Senate Amendment: H R 443 An Act to provide for the conveyance of certain property from the United States to the Maniilaq Association located in Kotzebue, Alaska
Bill 657 - Vote On Motion to Suspend the Rules and Concur in the Senate Amendment: H R 4212 Drywall Safety Act
Bill 658 - Vote On Agreeing to the Resolution: H RES 844 Providing for consideration of the Senate amendments to the bill (H.R. 8) to extend certain tax relief provisions enacted in 2001 and 2003, and to provide for expedited consideration of a bill providing for comprehensive tax reform, and for other purposes
Bill 659 - Vote On Motion to Concur in the Senate Amendments: H R 8 To extend certain tax relief provisions enacted in 2001 and 2003, and to provide for expedited consideration of a bill providing for comprehensive tax reform, and for other purposes
